Staring at the ceiling
I can feel you trying doors I'd opened up before
But I'm the one with all the keys
And I'm the one who's walking 'round here
Like I own the joints
Oh, I got ways to shake it off, baby
And as long as you stay intoxicated
I'll keep beating your heart until I break it
Because you can take it
I'm gonna go crazy, baby
I'ma play you
Play you right until the track's done
Play you however many times I want, yeah
I'll play you like a slow song
Yeah, I'll keep you spinning
Spinning circles 'til the groove's gone
And fade it out just like a setting sun, yeah
I'll play you like a slow song
You can flip back through the pages
And you won't find I was making any promises
You're the desert, I'm the rain
And we both know I never stay
But still you wanted it
Ooh, I got ways of losing you, baby
I'm faster than whatever you're chasing
I'll keep beating on your heart 'til I break it
And if you can take it, I'm gonna go crazy, baby
I'ma play you
Play you right until the track's done
Play you however many times I want, yeah
I'll play you like a slow song
Yeah, I'll keep you spinning
Spinning circles 'til the groove's gone
And fade it out just like a setting sun, yeah
I'll play you like a slow song
Keep you, keep you spinning 'round
Play you again and again
I'm gonna play you
Play you right until the track's done
Play you however many times I want, yeah
I'll play you like a slow song
Yeah, I'll keep you spinning
Spinning circles 'til the groove's gone
And fade it out just like a setting sun, yeah
I'll play you like a slow song
I wanna play you
(Keep you, keep you spinning 'round)
I'm gonna play you (play you again and again)
Play you so slow, baby (keep you, keep you spinning 'round)
(Play you again and again) until you get it right
(Keep you, keep you spinning 'round)
(Play you again and again) gonna play you
(Keep you, keep you spinning 'round) there's nothing
(I'll play you again and again)